usatodaysportsimages.com 2015-12-06

# USA TODAY Sports Images

The following Website Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") governs your use of the website located at www.usatodaysportsimages.com (the "Website"), which is owned and operated by USA TODAY Sports Images ("USA TODAY Sports Images," "we," "our" or "us").

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you. Please read the information below to learn more about our collection policies and practices.

When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information" we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your name, street address or email address. When other information is associated with personally identifiable information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

####  1\. TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED

We may collect the following types of information:

Information You Provide To Us: In the course of using the Website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information, such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number or fax number; unique identifiers, such as your username and user password; demographic information, such as your date of birth, age, gender, education, household income, occupation; or other similar information.

Site Usage Information: We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Website, such as your click-stream data and your IP address. See the "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data" section below.

Email Communications: When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation noting you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have opted to receive or not to receive.

####  2\. HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED

We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below:

Registration: You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a username and password. Participation in registration is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information to the Website.

Newsletters and Website Emails: We may offer free newsletters to share information with you about the Website, about us or about our marketing partners and advertisers and sponsors. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. You may also cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided on the Website or in the newsletter.

Contests or Sweepstakes: We may periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through the Website that may require registration or the submission of personally identifiable information. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information to the Website. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes. We may also ask your permission to allow us to publicly post some of your personally identifiable information on the Website, such as on a winner's page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes. Except as required by applicable law, we will not post your personally identifiable information without your permission.

Surveys or Voting: From time-to-time we may request personally identifiable information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information to the Website.

Cookies: As with many Websites, the Website uses a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a unique, random number that is stored in the browser on your computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify you, just the computer that is used to visit the Website. Cookies automatically identify your browser to the Website whenever your computer is used to visit the Website. Cookies also let us know how many people visit the Website and where visitors go on the Website. In addition, cookies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like what web browser is being used to access the Website. For registered users, cookies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Website are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Website. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, your browser should contain an option that allows you to disable or delete cookie data at any time. Some areas of the Website, however, may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies. Cookies are not tied to personally identifiable information on the Website.

IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data: We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data. An IP address is a number associated with the service through which you access the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to collect aggregate information. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information. Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request Web pages from the Website. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personally identifiable information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.

####  3\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:

  * contact you;
  * monitor or improve the use of the Website;
  * customize the content you see;
  * monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Website; and
  * send you promotional material or special offers.

####  4\. WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED

At times, we may share your personally identifiable information with others for various purposes. The following outlines the ways in which your information may be shared with others and the ways in which you may opt-out of having your information shared:

Agents: We may employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending email, removing repetitive information from our database, website analysis, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service. Such agents may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for their own purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.

Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website usage statistics, with other parties. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.

Other Promotional Offers: We may send offers to you on behalf of our marketing partners. When we do this, we do not give that partner your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, you may contact us. This can be done by sending an opt-out message in an email to [picturedesk@uspresswire.com](mailto:picturedesk@uspresswire.com).

Business Transfers: In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party or another transaction occurs in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred, all personally identifiable information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer.

Administrative or Legal Process: Your personally identifiable information may be transferred to third parties without notice to you in order to comply with applicable law, law enforcement agencies, to protect our rights or protect the rights of other users of the Website.

####  5\. SECURITY

The Website incorporates reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personally identifiable information that we may collect, and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and alteration. Your personally identifiable information is transferred to our computers utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required.

####  6\. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

You should be aware that when you are on the Website you could be directed to other Websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a link on the Website, the "click" may take you off the Website onto a different website. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personally identifiable information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to the Website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any personally identifiable information.

####  7\. A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY

The Website is a general audience Website. Currently, we do not intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen on the Website. If in the future we intend to collect personally identifiable information from children, we will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.).

####  8\. YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

By using the Website, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use and/or share your personally identifiable information, we will post a notice on the Website and / or send an email to users who have provided an email address. We will assume that you have given your permission for your information to be used under the terms of the new privacy policy, if you do not respond to our email within thirty days or continue to use the Website thirty days after a notice is posted. Please note that you should always update your personally identifiable information to provide us with a current email address.

####  9\. CORRECTING / UPDATING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

If your personally identifiable information changes or if you no longer desire to access the Website, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us. This can be done by sending an email to picturedesk@usatodaysportsimages.com or you may write us at USA TODAY Sports Images, 535 Madison Avenue, 20th Floor, New York, NY 10022, Attn: Internet Dept.

####  10\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

A California privacy law that went into effect on January 1, 2005, allows California residents to obtain specific information about a business's privacy practices if it shares information with other companies for those companies' direct marketing purposes.

As explained in this Privacy Policy, whenever you agree to let us collect personally identifiable information about you, we will always provide you with an option to prevent this information from being shared for non-administrative purposes with third parties. You can exercise this option at any time by following the steps outlined herein.

Because the Website has a comprehensive Privacy Policy and provides you with details on how you may opt-out of the use of your personally identifiable information by third parties for direct marketing purposes, we are not required to provide you with this information.

If you are a California resident and have questions about our compliance with this law, please send an email to picturedesk@usatodaysportsimages.com or you may write us at USA TODAY Sports Images, 535 Madison Avenue, 20th Floor, New York, NY 10022, Attn.: Internet Dept. - California Privacy Rights.

####  11\. QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of the Website, please send an email to picturedesk@usatodaysportsimages.com or you may write us at USA TODAY Sports Images, 535 Madison Avenue, 20th Floor, New York, NY 10022,  Attn: Internet Dept. - Privacy Policy.

Last Modified: December, 2012. Copyright 2012 USA TODAY Sports Images
